It's been five days
since we left the manor.
How long does it take to get to
Dirashik, where the magic school is?
We're still in the Kingdom of Hughlia.
At this rate, maybe a month.
That long? It's so far.
Yes, it is.
But we should be at
Grandfather's manor soon.
Say, Iko?
Yes?
Are you really sure this is it?
Yes, this is where we say goodbye.
I'd like to get married.
I'm already a bit past marriageable age,
so it's now or never.
If I give up now, I think I'll give up
on the idea for the rest of my life.
You think I can live on without you?
Will you marry me then, Master Kunon?
Will you leave Princess
Mirika and take me?
Oh, now I can see the manor.
FAREWELLS AND HELLOS AND DIRASHIK
It's been four years since
I came to visit the main family.
Wait, why did I come here four years ago?
Don't you remember?
Having heard that there
was a huge library here,
you thought there might be books on magic
and dragged your whole family here.
Wait, did I?
I won't stop dancing until
you say you'll take me there!
Darling, listen to Kunon.
Fine. I got it, Kunon.
I'll take you there!
Back then, you did everything you
could to learn magic, Master Kunon.
That's true.
Kunon!
Grandfather!
You've grown big!
I must always be a bigger
man than I was yesterday.
Indeed, indeed!
It's been four years. I've missed you so!
It's so good to see you!
Mother is a hero and Grandfather
is a demon lord, huh?
Is Tinalisa well?
Yes, she's doing so well she
could totally defeat you.
Very good, very good.
To celebrate your enrollment at the magic
school, I shall buy you anything you want.
Oh, no...
Lord Regent. I have a letter
for you from Lady Tinalisa.
No need to be shy.
You want gems? Jewels?
Let's call a jeweler here now.
Someone!
Lord Regent! Here's a
letter from your daughter!
I must not spend over five
hundred thousand necca on Kunon?
It's not a child's allowance!
A twelve-year-old is a child.
Two months of my salary.
It's fine if she doesn't find out, right?
Grandfather.
What, you want it secretly?
Shall I buy you a large vessel secretly?
No, please send for my new maid.
I'm here so she can take over from Iko.
You're right.
I'll go get her.
I'm Rinko Round! I'm eighteen!
I applied for this job because
the pay wasn't too bad!
I want to open my own store in the future
and also save up for wedding expenses,
so I agreed to this position!
Well, um... Nice to meet you.
You're Iko's little sister, right?
Yes. My sister recommended this job to me.
By the way, I already have
a fiancé, unlike her.
You want me to beat you up?
No, that's not what I mean.
I'm saying I'm not open to
being contracted as a mistress.
You don't have to worry about that.
I have a fiancée as well,
so you should cherish your fiancé
more than the three mealtimes of the day.
I will!
Wait, my mealtimes...?
You don't want to?
I will do my best!
We promised that we'd
open the store together.
And I need money for that, too!
You two are alike.
I was worried you might not
get my sense of humor.
People have called us lively
sisters since we were small.
Looking forward to serving you!
They do look alike.
I was nervous since you told me
he was the scion of a marquis
and a sorcerer with a Hero's Scar,
but he seems easygoing.
When he's focused on magic,
he forgets to eat.
So make him sandwiches so
he can eat while he studies.
His favorite sandwiches are Hamburg
steak and bacon, you said?
Yes. And milk tea.
Ask if he wants it without
milk or without tea.
Oh, I know I'll get along just fine.
Yes, I'm sure you will.
You want me to attend Master Kunon?
Your reputation precedes you.
What?! Am I famous?!
Will I get swarmed by suitors?
Oh, I'm still young and I'm not ready!
That's what we need.
I thought he could use someone like you.
Nice to meet you, Master Kunon.
My name is Iko, and I will be
taking care of you starting today.
Iko?
Yes!
That's lettuce.
Lettuce?
And what's this?
It's mustard.
Wow, so dashing!
Master Kunon, perhaps you were the
model for the classic storybook prince?
Alas, my true identity has been revealed.
I'm sorry for not telling you the truth.
Plus, you'll be perfectly
fine on your own now.
I won't be.
Miss Jenié left me, Lady Flora left me,
and if you leave me, too...
Rinko.
Yeah?
Master Kunon is still a child.
He's earnest and listens
to people around him.
So I'm telling you, if you put
any weird ideas in his head,
you'll have me to answer to.
I'll beat you up if you
teach him anything naughty.
Anything naughty?
Like chasing skirts?
Stop it! I don't want to hear it!
Master Kunon is the sweetest angel!
And if some random cunning, dingy
wench comes in contact with him...
No, I can't stand the thought!
Princess Mirika is the only one who
is allowed to touch him as a woman!
Only Princess Mirika!
I got it.
I'll watch out for his
relationships with women.
But you know, Master Kunon is a
gentleman, so he's kind to women.
He almost always speaks to them
and gives them compliments,
so he's just an easy target
for women, you know?
Why do you describe him so terribly?
Because that's what you told me.
I mean, it only follows that
he'll become a womanizer.
Stop it! Master Kunon would never do that!
He's an angel!
Come on, let's be real.
Why are you so obsessed—
He won't!
Master Kunon would never!
Mmm, it's tasty!
Especially this bacon.
Smoked by the warmth and
love of you two sisters,
I feel like even I'm getting
smokey and aromatic.
See what I mean?
He will not!
Good morning, Master Kunon.
It's time for your departure.
Yes.
Iko.
Yes?
Do you remember what I said after
Miss Jenié and Lady Flora quit?
That I'd never be fine if you left me.
Yes.
Right now, I'm away from
Father, Mother, Big Brother,
the Royal Sorcerers, and my master...
not to mention Princess Mirika.
And now I'll be away from you
and go to the magic school.
But this is what I wanted
and decided for myself.
Yes.
You'll be away from me, but we're
only apart. You won't be gone. Right?
That's right. You can see
me when you come home.
I will continue this work in
Hughlia after I get married.
It'll be a few years until I see you next.
By then, I may have a child.
An adorable child like you.
Please take care, Master Kunon.
Thank you for everything, Iko.
Are you sure you must go?
You don't have to, Kunon.
Why don't you live here with me?
Start the carriage.
See you!
Kunon, wait for me!
Kunon!
Are you sure it was fine to leave?
The lord regent was still
saying something to you.
If I respond, it will only
take longer, so it's fine.
Anyhow, thank you for coming
to work for me, Rinko.
It's my pleasure!
Your fiancé will have to wait for
several years. Are you sure you're okay?
Yes! He said he'd wait, since it
was to make money for our store.
What kind of store is it going to be?
A shady business of sweeping
people under the rug?
I did think about that,
but I decided on a restaurant.
I like eating, and they're kind of
the same thing. Plus, it's legal.
You're right. The only difference is
sustaining people with food or
getting rid of them in the dark.
A new life begins.
I'm starting everything anew.
And I will meet new people.
Yeah, this isn't too bad.
Wow, so many magic stores!
Because it's close to Dirashik.
Which means Dirashik is a
nation of amazing magic?
Are all these books on magic? Incredible!
The lord regent's library was way bigger.
But didn't have a lot of books on magic.
I've only read a handful so far.
Would you like to buy some now, then?
We'll end up on the streets.
What? Um...
5 MILLION NECCA
Really?!
What is this price?!
The book alone can cover a store for me
and my fiancé, plus a branch store!
Magic books are one of a kind.
That's why each book costs a fortune.
It's too expensive!
Rinko, you shouldn't be
too loud in a store—
Are you a sorcerer, too?
A student at the magic
school by any chance?
I'm an applicant.
Can you use magic, then?
What attribute?
Water.
Show me, show me!
Sure, if it's a request from a lady.
A-ori.
Wow, so tiny!
So cute!
This is amazing!
Thank you very much.
Are you a sorcerer as well?
No, I just love magic, and I really
wanted to work in the field of magic.
I guess I'm a magic enthusiast.
My gosh, today is my day!
To meet a sorcerer who can
use such adorable spell!
Dirashik is intense these days,
so best of luck to you.
Intense?
Yeah. This year, the saint of the
Holy Kingdom is enrolling as well.
The Saint.
Last year, they had the Inferno Prince and
Lightning Bolt of the New Kingdom.
And now you're joining them.
You'll be so famous!
Wow, I'm looking forward to it.
Oh, I know!
I just got a secondhand grimoire of the
most popular sorcerer, Zeonly Finroll.
I'll give you a special discount.
Oh, no thank you.
What? Why?
MUMBLE MUMBLE MUMBLE MUMBLE
This single book is worth
my store, my dream...
I didn't realize it would
shock you that much.
Of course it did.
By the way, that grimoire
really was a great bargain.
Are you sure you don't want it?
It's fine. I know the contents, and
it's most likely the clean copy I made.
What?
What should I check out next?
Oh no. This well-dressed child
with a maid came into the store,
and now he's touching the merchandise.
What's going on?!
Excuse me, sir?
Excuse me, ma'am?
Woo-hoo!
Um...
A veggie thief will hang, you hear me?
Rinko, this is great.
It's not great!
What do you think you're doing?
Stop touching my merchandise!
Oh, please pay me no mind.
I have to! I can't help it!
I was trying to memorize the texture.
Simple words like "cloth" and
"fur" can cover diverse textures.
Texture?
What fur is this?
It's dark fox.
It's very rare, so please do not touch it—
A-ori.
A dark fox?!
I'm sorry, I should have asked for
your permission before I did this.
You can reproduce animals
with magic? I see.
Can you reproduce anything
if you know the texture?
Yes. Reproducing only
shape and texture, though.
Then... what about a woman?
The hell are you suggesting to a child?!
No, I'm sorry!
Sorry isn't gonna cut it, tainting
precious Master Kunon's ears!
Reproducing a human is
too complicated, so no.
And I get yelled at so much.
Let's go, Master Kunon.
This store is for trashy adults!
I'm so sorry!
I only asked on impulse!
I-I have a crush on this lady,
and I gave into the temptation
that maybe I could lay with her!
Shut your piehole!
You'll taint Master Kunon's heart, too.
This town is bad for your education!
Let us hurry to Dirashik!
When you're mad, you're scarier than Iko.
What did I utter toward a child...?
Oh, welcome.
Wonderful to see you, Your Reverence.
I've been told that you have
a rare scarf made of dark fox.
May I see it?
A dark fox?
I thought they didn't like humans.
Oh, this? This is...
It's a spell.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't
expect it to be water.
That dark fox was water?
Water attribute magic?
E-Excuse me...
Do not move!
I'm sorry!
The way it burst, it seemed it was
made with small amount of magical power.
That child and now these people.
What kind of torturous day is it today?!
It's a spell outside of my knowledge.
We're here!
We're in Dirashik, Master Kunon!
Yes!
I'm finally here at the magic school!
You must be tired from the
long journey, Master Kunon.
Please rest well today.
Yes. Same to you, Rinko.
Master Kunon, you'll
live in a dorm, right?
Basically, all students at the
magic school will live in the dorm.
If we ask, an attendant
can live with us.
I'm sorry, but the dorm is full
and there's no vacancy.
What?!
The application for the
dorm is long past due.
You didn't know?
Master never mentioned that to me.
What a bold entrance.
Was it meant to shock me?
Or are you here to play?
I need to speak to you. Urgently.
It's about my beloved student.
This is bad.
Indeed.
Would you like to stay at a hotel?
The funds from your family can cover that.
Hmm. Since I'll be here for several
years while attending the magic school,
can I rent a house for longer stay?
I'm sure there will be expenses
for magic-related stuff,
so I'd like to save where I can.
What do you think? Rent a
small house and live together?
What?! Is this a proposal?
Excuse me.
Information on real estate agents?
We give it out to the applicants
who couldn't get into the dorm.
The real estate agents on that list
can show you some
nice properties for sorcerers.
Wow!
A life for just the two of us begins!
Come in.
I've brought the list
of incoming students.
I hear we have the cream
of the crop this year.
Yes. Some are eligible
for the Advanced class.
Hm?
Apparently he's a student of Zeonly.
Hm. That man took a student, huh?
Kunon Gurion.
ENTRANCE EXAM CHECK-IN
I can't enter?
Right. No one can enter except for the
students and authorized people.
Would this help, by any chance?
No, it won't.
Please watch your step.
Thank you very much.
You look strict, but you're
actually very kind, my lady.
"My lady"...
Forgive me.
I'm afraid I don't know what to call you,
but not having a name is also tantalizing.
Not having a name?
I have a name, and it's Loubella... oh.
What a beautiful name.
The sounds of "lou" and "bella"
are especially excellent.
As if you took "lou" and
"bella" and put them together.
The maid was something else,
but this child is also...
Please wait here.
An eyepatch?
And a cane.
This is exciting.
Next episode: "The Advanced Class."
NEXT EPISODE: THE ADVANCED CLASS